Guide to the John McCarthy Papers SC0524
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Original Accession, Accession ARCH-1995-247
  - "The Future Study on the Impact of Computers and Information Processing," 1976 (draft report) (Box 31)
  - "Advanced Digital Processor Technology Base Development For Navy Applications: The S-1 Project," Sep 1977 (report) (Box 31)
  - "Advanced Digital Processor Technology Base Development For Navy Applications: The S-1 Project," Sep 1978 (report) (Box 32)
  - S-1 Architecture Manual, Jan 1979 (Box 32)
  - SRA (Science Research Association) Management Briefing," 1987 (videotape) (Box 32)
  - "High Def. TV Seminar: Dr. John McCarthy," 1989 (videotape) (Box 32)
  - "Artificial Intelligence and Electronic Data Exchange," (videotape) (Box 32)
  - Transitions Research Corp., "NASA Phase II SBIR Final Report Video," May 1990 (Box 32)
  - "Helpmate Update," Jun 1990 (videotape) (Box 32)
  - Two reels of film, unidentified (Box 32)
  - "Carry Tape Dump of Peano:> JMC > ** > ***," 1987 (data cartridge) (Box 32)
  - "Research Directions in Software Technology," ed. Peter Wegner, The MIT Press, 1979 (Box 32)
  - "JMC Lib DUMP," June 1978 (correspondence, articles, program listings) (Box 33)
  - "JMC Lib DUMP," June 1978 (correspondence, articles, program listings) (Box 34)
  - "Microcode #534, 9 trk, 800 BPI, Digital Equipment Corp., 1976 (magnetic tape) (Box 35)
  - "System: 1026; Contents: SUDS FAILSAFE 1, 2; Nov 29, 1975; 7trk, 800 BPI, Drive: MTA1; STR: DSK; Who: Helliwell," (magnetic tape) (Box 35)
  - "Stanford Comp. Ctr., copy of #295, 4/15" (magnetic tape) (Box 35)
  - "Mag 19, 2/67; 7 trk, 800 BPI (magnetic tape) (Box 35)
  - Audio cassettes: (Box 36)
  - "Machines with Minds" - program 1, March 11, 1983 (Box 36)
  - "Machines with Minds"- program 2, March 11, 1983 (Box 36)
  - "Machines with Minds" - program 3, March 18, 1983 (Box 36)
  - "Machines with Minds" - program 4, March 25, 1983 (Box 36)
  - "Machines with Minds" - program 5, March 30, 1983 (Box 36)
  - Jerrold Katz, "An Outline of Platonist Grammar" - TIN Lunch, April 9, 1984 (Box 36)
  - AAAI Presidential Speech, 8/9/84, Tape I (Box 36)
  - AAAI Presidential Speech, 8/9/84, Tape II (Box 36)
  - IJCA.SPE[e 85, jmc] (Box 36)
  - John McCarthy side of interview with Wally Johns of Christian Science Monitor radio (Box 36)
  - Stanford A. I. Foonly Group. Wire-wrap card designs, n.d. (Box 37)
  - Earnest Video Switch--wiring diagrams, 1971 (Box 37)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1996-060
  - M.I.T. correspondence, papers, memos, booklets (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - M.I.T. booklets, memos, reports (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Mathematical Reviews (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Requests for Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Untitled (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Texas, Univ. of (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - US Exchange Program with USSR (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Electrical Engineering Meetings (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Other Comp. Sci. Dept (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Natasha [Rodman] (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Meeting (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Math Reviews (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - References [letters of] (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1966 Oct-1967 Dec (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - POP-1 to India (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Computer Science Exams--University of Edinburgh (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Comp. Sci. Dept. Meetings (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - HAND (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - General correspondence (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - FUND (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - EYE (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Ito, Takayasu (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - FOL Manual (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Unfunded Proposals (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Unfunded Proposals (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Unfunded Proposals (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Photographs (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Student papers (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - McCarthy "Technology and the Enhancement of Man", 1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Computer Printouts (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Multilisp manuals (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - LOTS (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Stanford LISP 1.6 Manual (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Artificial Intelligence Laboratory: various reports, manuals, memos, 1958-1982 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - "Global Trends in Computer Technology and Their Impact on Export Control," Committee to Study International Development in Computer Science and Technology, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Various manuals and technical reports by Stanford and other institutions, 1972-1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Books and reports not in Russian and French (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Notebook: Stanford personnel information (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Notebook: Office manual, secretary (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Xerox: Technical Review Panel Meeting at Palo Alto Research Center (notebook), 1974 Nov (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Memorabilia (certificates and plaques) (Box 5)
  - Note cards, audio cassette, four computer tapes (Box 5)
  - MACLISP Reference Manual, 1977 (Box 5)
  - Honorary Doctorate, Universidad Politécnica de Madrid, 1991 Jan 28 (Box 6)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1999-053
  - Home Terminals Revisited (Box 1)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2008-356
  - Honorary degree from Harvard, 2008 (Box 1)
- Additional Material [computer files], circa 1975-2008; Accession ARCH-2009-218; 1689.6 megabyte(s); 22769 computer files saved as two Unix .tar files.
  Other Finding Aids
  Preliminary computer file directory (.pdf)
- Celebration of John McCarthy's Accomplishments [computer files], 2012 Mar 25; Accession ARCH-2012-040; 218 megabyte(s) (161 files in 13 directories)
- Website, 2010 Dec 9; 60.6 megabyte(s) (5,497 files in 206 directories)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2012-055
  - Chronological Files
    - Correspondence, 1979
    - 1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1982 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1983 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 1983 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1983 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 1983 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Jan 1984-Aug 84 (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Jan 1984-Aug 84 (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - September 1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - October 1984 (1 of 3) (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - October 1984 (2 of 3) (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - October 1984 (3 of 3) (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - November 1984-Dec 84 (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - November 1984-Dec 84 (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - January 85 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Mar-May 1985 (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Mar-May 1985 (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - February 1985 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - May 1985 (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - May 1985 (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - June 1985 (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - June 1985 (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - July 1985 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Aug 22/1985 (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Aug 22/1985 (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Aug 1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Sept 85 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - November 1985 (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - November 1985 (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - December 1985 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - January 86 (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - January 86 (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - February 1986 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - March 86 (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - March 86 (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - April 86 (1 of 4) (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - April 86 (2 of 4) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - April 86 (3 of 4) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - April 86 (4 of 4) (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - May-June 5 1986 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - June 24 - August 31, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - 0725E86 - July 86 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - 0715E85 - July 86 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - 0710E86 - July 86 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - 0707E86 - July 86 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - September 1986 (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - September 1986 (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - October 1986 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Nov 1986 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - December 1986 (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - December 1986 (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - January 1987 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - 12/16/86 - 12/31/86 (1 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - 12/16/86 - 12/31/86 (2 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - 12/16/86 - 12/31/86 (3 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Feb March 1987 (1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Feb March 1987 (2 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - March 18, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - April 1987 (1 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - April 1987 (2 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - April 1987 (3 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - May 1987 (1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - May 1987 (2 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - June 1987 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - July 1987 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - August 14, 1987 (1 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - August 14, 1987 (2 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - August 15, 1987 (1 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - August 15, 1987 (2 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - August 15, 1987 (3 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - August 28-9, 1987 (1 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - August 28-9, 1987 (2 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - August 30-31, 1987 (1 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - August 30-31, 1987 (2 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - August 30-31, 1987 (1 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - October 1987 File 1 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - October 1987 File 2 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - October 1987 File 3 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - October 1987 File 4 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - October 1987 File 3 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - November 1987 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - November 1987 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - November 1987 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - December 1987 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - December 1987 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - December 1987 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - December 1987 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - March 1988 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - February 1988 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - January 1988 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - March 20, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - March 1988 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - March 25, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - May 13, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - May 14, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - May 25, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - May 26, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - June 22, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - June 23, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - July 10, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - July 12, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - July 14, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - July 16, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - July 18, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - September 6, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - October 3, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - October 4, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - October 15, 1988 (1 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - October 15, 1988 (2 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - November 1988 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - December 1988 (1 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - December 1988 (2 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - January 1989 (1 of 5) (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - January 1989 (2 of 5) (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - January 1989 (3 of 5) (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - January 1989 (4 of 5) (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - January 1989 (5 of 5) (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - February 1989 (1 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - February 1989 (2 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - February 1989 (3 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - 2003 Dec L (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - 2003 Dec. M (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - 2004 Mar A (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - 2004 Mar. B (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - 2004 Mar. C (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - 2004 Mar. D (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - 2004 Apr. A (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - 2004 Mar. E (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - 2004 May A (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - 2004 May B (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - 2004 Jun. A (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - 2004 Jun. B (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - 2004 Jun. C (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - 2004 June D (1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - 2004 Jun D (2 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - ARPA Reports (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - 2004 Jun E-2 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Elephant (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Data Mining Slides (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - 2004 Jun F-1 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - 1979 Notes - Linguistics (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - 2004 Jun F-3 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Humar (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - 2004 Jun F-5 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - 2004 Jun-G (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - 2004 Jun-H (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - 2004 Jun H (2 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - 2004 Jun I (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - 2004 Jul A (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Lisp Book (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - 2004 July B (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - 2004 July C (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Chess (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - May 91 (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - May 91 (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Jun 91 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Jul 91 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Jul 91 (2) (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - August 91 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Sep 91 (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Sep 91 (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Sep 91 (3) (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Oct 91 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Dec 91 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Jan 92 (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Jan 92 (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Jan 92 (2) (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Jan 92 (2) (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Feb 92 (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Feb 92 (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Mar 92 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - April 92 1 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - April 92 2 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - April 92 3 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - April 92 4 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - April 92 5 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - April 92 6 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - April 92 7 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - April 92 8 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - April 92 9 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - May 92 1 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - May 92 2 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - May 92 3 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - May 92 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Jun 92 1 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Jun 92 2 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Jun 92 3 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Jul 92 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Aug 92 1 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Aug 92 2 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Aug 92 3 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Sep 92 (1 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Sep 92 (2 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Oct 92 1 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Oct 92 2 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Oct 92 3 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Dec 92 1 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Dec 92 2 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Dec 92 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - November 93 (1 of 3) (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - November 93 (2 of 3) (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - November 93 (3 of 3) (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Dec 93 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Jan 94 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Feb 94 (1 of 3) (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Feb 94 (2 of 3) (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Mar 94 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Apr 94 1 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Apr 94 2 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Apr 94 3 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Apr 94 4 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Apr 94 5 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - May 94 (1 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - May 94 (2 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - June 94 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - July 94 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Aug 94 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Jan 95 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Mar 95 1 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Mar 95 2 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Mar 95 3 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Mar 95 4 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Mar 95 5 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Mar 95 6 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - April 95 1 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - April 95 2 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - April 95 3 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - May 95 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - May 95 1 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - May 95 2 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - May 95 3 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - May 95 4 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - May 95 5 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - May 95 6 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - June 95 1 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - June 95 2 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - June 95 3 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - June 95 4 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - June 95 5 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Aug 1995 (1 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Aug 1995 (2 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Sept 95 (1 of 3) (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Sept 95 (2 of 3) (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Sept 95 (3 of 3) (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Oct 95 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Nov 95 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Dec 95 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Feb 96 1 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Feb 96 2 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Feb 96 3 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Feb 96 4 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Feb 96 5 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Feb 96 6 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Feb 96 7 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Feb 96 8 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Feb 96 9 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Feb 96 10 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Feb 96 11 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Feb 96 12 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Feb 96 13 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Feb 96 14 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Feb 96 15 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Feb 96 16 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Feb 96 17 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Feb 96 18 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Mar 96 1 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Mar 96 2 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - April 96 1 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - April 96 2 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - April 96 3 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - May 1996 (1 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - May 1996 (2 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - June 1996 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - July 1996 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - March 1989 (1 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - March 1989 (2 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - April 1989 (1 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - April 1989 (2 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - May 1989 (1 of 3) (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - May 1989 (2 of 3) (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - May 1989 (3 of 3) (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - June 1989 (1 of 3) (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - June 1989 (2 of 3) (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - June 1989 (3 of 3) (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - July 1989 (1 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - July 1989 (2 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - August 1989 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - September 1989 (1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - September 1989 (2 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - October 1989 1 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - October 1989 2 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - October 1989 3 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - October 1989 4 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - November 1989 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - December 1989 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - January 1990 1 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - January 1990 2 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - January 1990 3 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - January 1990 4 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - January 1990 5 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - January 1990 6 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - February 1990 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - May 1990 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - June 1990 (1 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - June 1990 (2 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - July 1990 1 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - July 1990 2 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - July 1990 3 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - August 1990 1 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - August 1990 2 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - October 1990 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - November 1990 1 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - November 1990 2 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - November 1990 3 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - November 1990 4 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - November 1990 5 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - November 1990 6 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - November 1990 7 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - November 1990 8 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - November 1990 9 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - November 1990 10 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - March 1990 1 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - March 1990 2 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - March 1990 3 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - December 1990 1 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - December 1990 2 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - December 1990 3 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - December 1990 4 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - December 1990 5 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - December 1990 6 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - December 1990 7 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - December 1990 8 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - December 1990 9 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - December 1990 10 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - December 1990 11 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - January 1991 1 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - January 1991 2 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - January 1991 3 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - March 1991 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - April 1991 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - May 1991 (1 of 2) (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - May 1991 (2 of 2) (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - January 1993 1 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - January 1993 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - January 1993 3 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - January 1993 4 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - February 1993 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - March 1993 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - April 1993 1 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - April 1993 2 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - April 1993 3 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - May 1993 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - June 1993 1 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - June 1993 2 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - June 1993 3 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - June 1993 4 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - NWSMC June 23-24 1993 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - July 1993 (1 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - July 1993 (2 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - August 1993 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Sept 1993 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - October 1993 1 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - October 1993 2 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - October 1993 3 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - January 1998 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - February/March 1998 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - April 1998 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - May 1998 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - June 1998 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - July 1998 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Sept 1998 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - October 1998 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - November 1998 (1 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - November 1998 (2 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - August 1996 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - September 1996 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - October 1996 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - November 1996 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - December 1996 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - January 1997 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - March 1997 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - May 1997 (1 of 3) (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - May 1997 (2 of 3) (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - May 1997 (3 of 3) (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - June 1997 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - August 1997 1 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - August 1997 2 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - August 1997 3 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - August 1997 4 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - September 1997 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - October 1997 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - November 1997 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - December 1997 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - January 1999 (1 of 3) (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - January 1999 (2 of 3) (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - January 1999 (3 of 3) (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - February 1999 (1 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - February 1999 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - March 1999 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - May 1999 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - July 1999 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - August '99 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - September '99 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Flavell (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - November 1999 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Time Blind (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - December 1999 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - January 2000 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - February 2000 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - March 2000 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Quantum (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Kurklu (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - May 2000 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - June 2000 (1 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - June 2000 (2 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - July 2000 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - August 2000 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - September 2000 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - October 2000 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - November 2000 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - December 2000 (1 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - December 2000 (2 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Jan 2001 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Feb-March 2001 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - April 2001 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - May 2001 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - July 2001 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - October 2001 (Part 1) (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - October 2001 (Part 2) (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - November 2001 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - December 2001 Part 1 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - December 2001 Part 2 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - December 2001 Part 3 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Jan 2002 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Chron April 2002 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Sept 2002 (1 of 3) (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Sept 2002 (2 of 3) (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Sept 2002 (3 of 3) (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - January 2003 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - May 2003 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - July 2003 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - December 2003 1 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - December 2003 2 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - December 2003 3 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - December 2003 4 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - December 2003 5 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - December 2003 6 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - December 2003 7 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - December 2003 8 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - December 2003 9 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Non-Monotone Reasoning files
    - Non-Mono Dups A-F (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Non-Mono Dups G-L (Box 29, Folder 6)